[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ":", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "What have you found since getting there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "What I found, Piers, is something amazing, that local people -- lawyers, businessmen and others -- have set up what amounts to an ad hoc government with committees dealing everything, food supply, public health, even garbage collection.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Could this be over quickly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "It's not clear but it's a much more complicated situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "I am well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Does it feel weird being on that side of the desk?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "A little.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Do you like it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "What did you make of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "What's your overview of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I think he may not last.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Which is extraordinary, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "You think he's the kind of character that would?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "I don't think he's going to run.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Do you feel more able to give opinion now out of the nightly show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Not really, no, because I'm going to do other things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "If I asked you what you thought of Obama and how he's getting on, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "I would say he had a difficult start.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "What do you think would happen if they do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "They would win.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Where did he finish?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Well, it's actually interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald"]}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "I mean Trump does have kind of appeal, doesn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "ING: But he -- I love Donald, but he does this every election.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kennedy"]}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Who did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "CNN poll -- I think Kennedy won.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Who would be the one in your lifetime that you think was the most effective president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Clinton.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Have you read the full quote?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "I'm dangerous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 239, "question": "I thought you are -- what you did was or what they did -- were you being facetious when you said I was dangerous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Well, look --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Was that an attempt at British humor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Let me ask you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "RB", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "How many of my shows have you watched?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "About -- now about eight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "You have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I haven't seen you dangerous yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "What's wrong with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "I suppose I've always oversold myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "That's not strictly true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "When you said dangerous, what did you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "I think -- I was only kidding.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "British humor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Yes, it is British.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "What are the things that when you wake up you think, wow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "I miss asking questions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "You did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "No, twice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "For screaming at the officials?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "Two things ticked me about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Do you ever hit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Have you got that in you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Why do you think the ratings fell in the way that they did in your last couple of years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I think television changed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "You know it's like the old joke about enough about me, let's talk about you, what do you think of me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "I thought -- you've always got to quit leaving the public wanting more, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "You shed a tear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "It was tough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Wait a minute.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "These are diamonds?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "You bet your ass they are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Where did you get that ring?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Richard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Or is it seven times?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Seven times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Did you ever think it might have been easy if the two of you just got together early?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Never thought of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "In a good way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "What do you -- I mean are you an incurable romantic at heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "I like romance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "For how long?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Until the flower guy said, you know, she leaves a note, just leave it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Is this the last time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "I'm going to -- we're going to have some announcements coming?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Yes, tell me what you're up to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["April"], "LOCATION": ["Torrington", "Connecticut"]}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "And when is your stand-up tour starting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "It starts in April in Torrington, Connecticut, and I'm going to do comedy and talk about life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "What's that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Well, this is a little gift for you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Do they call them braces?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Suspenders are for lady's underwear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "So I've been wearing lady's underwear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "That's what the Brits think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Let me ask you both -- and maybe start with you Alicia, why do you believe that it was the damage to Dave's head that caused what happened to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", ":", "CC", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Dave was a brilliant man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alicia", "Dave"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dave"]}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "POS", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "So, clearly, when he wrote that, he believed that the -- what he had suffered since giving up football had made him reach the point of wanting to take his life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "I wouldn't say -- I don't know if -- I don't want to put word's in Dave's mouth, if that's the real reason he took his life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Do you remember when he came home after those games, what kind of condition he was in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Sometimes he would come home and he had extreme headaches, dizziness, and he was just tired and he would want to just lay down for a while and just relax.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "You suffered a concussion yourself, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "I did, playing in high school.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NFL"]}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "Do you think it's a credible link between that kind of impact damage and the depression and brain damage that follows afterwards?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "I think these guys that are playing in the NFL now are very large and very fast.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Let me ask you, Tregg, what kind of man was your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "He was a great man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tregg"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dave"]}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Alicia, what would you say about Dave now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "I would say that I'm very proud of Dave, that even in his darkest moment that he thought of others, and he wanted to help future athletes, future players that would come into the sport.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dave"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Amazingly, piers, the research is still pretty early.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "What do you make of what you heard from Sanjay?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "I make what he says is very correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sanjay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Tregg, let me ask you, finally, when you think of your father, does any part of you now wish he had never played NFL?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "Well, I mean, I would want my father to do what he loved.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tregg", "Odis", "David"]}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "It's not going to get any better, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "I asked Tregg and Odis, who was a player with David, that same question yesterday.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "What are you feeling now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "It was much tougher on Lindsay than it was on us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "Justifiably, no doubt, 100 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 788, "question": "Will that be a wake up call for all of you, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 789, "answer": "It's been a wake up call for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 802, "question": "Does Lindsay know she's going to jail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 803, "answer": "She's afraid she is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lindsay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 804, "question": "Her lawyer said to you this is pretty likely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 805, "answer": "OHAN: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 827, "question": "Do you think she's innocent of stealing the jewelry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 828, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 833, "question": "Is she scared, Michael?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 834, "answer": "Of course she is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "Do you think she could cope with being in jail, given the state that she's reached?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Billy Ray Cyrus"]}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 847, "question": "Do you think becoming famous and wealthy just made the whole situation ten times worse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 848, "answer": "People ask me that because they compare me to Billy Ray Cyrus, what he's going through.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 874, "question": "Will you come back again and talk more about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 875, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]